It's about the choices you make next.
Mom at Sixteen is a tv movie, drama film directed by Peter Werner.
Pregnant sixteen year old Jacey's well-meaning mother forces her to keep
the birth a secret and decides to raise the baby as her own.
Jacey Jeffries, played by Danielle Panabaker.
Donna Cooper, played by Jane Krakowski.
Macy, played by Clare Stone.
Brad, played by Tyler Hynes.
Bob, played by Colin Ferguson.
Terry Jeffries, played by Mercedes Ruehl.
Mom at Sixteen is a 2005 Lifetime Television film about a sixteen-year-old mother, dealing with problems at school and her decaying
relationship with her mother, because of her seeing her boyfriend for the first time since before her son was born.
The film explores themes of baby, teenage
pregnancy, pregnant teen, secret pregnancy.
The tone is emotional.